

**PRIYANSHU SHARMA** Analyst / Software Engineer



am an individual with a keen interest in Software programs, possessing interpersonal and analytical skills, who wish to use technical knowledge catering to the needs of the company. I wish to work with a diverse group of people and see myself heading a group of people over a 1-year duration in the company



KEY SKILLS

- Basic SQL
- HTML, CSS
- C++, C, Python,
- MS Excel
- · Power Point Presentation

8800804165

Priyanshu.c.sharma@capgemini.com

**EXPERIENCE** 

**ANALYST** (APR 2022 - Present) **CAPGEMINI** - Bangalore

## **VEGETATION CLASSIFICATION BASED ON LEAF PATTERN – ACADEMIC PROJECT**

(JAN 2020 - APR 2020)

- Objective is to create an application that can identify any species of leaf.
- Our system will identify whether the leaf will belong to some species or it's a new one.

## SOFTWARE AND HARDWARE SPECIFICATION

- Frameworks: Matplotlib, keras, TensorFlow
- Alogorithm: CNN(Convolutional Neural Network)
- Language: Python





**EDUCATION** 

B.Tech.

(2017 - 2021)

IMS ENGINEERING COLLEGE, GHAZIABAD

SPECIALIZATION- INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY



## **CERTIFICATIONS**

| Course                           | Platform |
|----------------------------------|----------|
| Channel Management and Retailing | Coursera |
| C++ and C programming            | DUCAT    |